SHELDON:
A word of warning:
(Sheldon:)My guest is a noted physicist...
(Sheldon:)...and the leading expert
on quantum cosmology...
(Sheldon:)...so please try to avoid wasting her time
with female gibber-gabber.
Female gibber-gabber?
(Sheldon:)Shoe sales, hair styles, mud masks...
(Sheldon:)...gossip about your friends,
Brad and Angelina.
PENNY:
No, they're not my friends.
SHELDON: Not surprised, considering how
you talk about them behind their backs.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
(Leonard:)She's here. She's here.
How do I look? Do I look smart?
(Sheldon:)Oh, good grief. This isn't about you.
(Sheldon:)Coming.
(Sheldon:)Now, listen, one of the great minds
of the 21st century...
(Sheldon:)...is about to play host to one of the
other great minds of the 21st century.
(Sheldon:)So pay attention.
(Sheldon:)Years from now, my biographer
might ask you about this event.
Well, I have so many things
to tell your biographer.
Oh, Dr. Cooper, thank goodness.
(Elizabeth:)I completely forgot your address.